ourordinarylife.com 2019-04-15

# Privacy Policy

Our website address is: https://ourordinarylife.com.

This privacy policy tells you how we use personal information collected at this site. Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information. By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. These practices may be changed, but any changes will be posted and changes will only apply to activities and information on a going forward, not retroactive basis. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.

We currently operate with no ad networks so will not collect information for ad purposes. We do collect data for spam protection.

**Who we are:** I am Kristin Lesney and my husband is Del Ruiz and together re operate OurOrdinaryLife.com out of Cypress, CA. My contact is Kristin@ourordinarylife.com.

_**What personal data we collect and why we collect it**_

**Comments:**  When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.

**Cookies:  **If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.  
If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.

When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.

If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.

**Analytics:** We use Google Analytics and StatCounter. Find their privacy policies here: GOOGLE https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en – STATCOUNTER  https://statcounter.com/about/legal/

**Your Rights Over Your Data:**  If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.

**Where We Send Your Data:  **Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.

**_Ninja Forms allows us to collect personal information, BUT only what you leave with us._**

_If you have any questions or concerns please contact me._

Our website address is: https://ourordinarylife.com.
